

KATELYNN SCHWERDTFEGER

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

Profile

I am a creative and professional cyber security consultant with experience in Netskope Administration, machine learning, data analysis, and website design. I have strong creative and analytical skills and I am working towards my Google UX Design Certification.

EXPERIENCE

CLOUD SECURITY ANALYST

Cloudrise Inc.

2021 - Present

- Worked with team members to help implement the Netskope SSE solution to companies on a global scale
- Documented project tasks and organized upcoming activities for four to six client projects on a weekly basis
- Conducted virtual client meetings to report project progress

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Colorado Mesa University Cybersecurity Center

2020 - 2021

- Worked with a team to publish research on DNS over HTTPS traffic found through machine learning experiments.
- The completed research paper can be found at https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?arnumber=9540699

WEBSITE DESIGN INTERN

Bear Byte Studios

2020

- Website design for various local clients
- Used a creator tool to generate accessible and responsive websites

970-683-0020

 \searrow

write2katelynns@gmail.com



654 Trinity Way Grand Junction, CO 81505



linkedin.com/in/katelynn-schwerdtfeger/

EDUCATION

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Colorado Mesa University Summa Cum Laude

2018 - 2022

SKILLS

- Bilingual (Spanish)
- User-centered research
- · Basic HTML and CSS
- Wireframe creation
- · Basics of Figma and Adobe CC
- Agile SDL method
- Flexible problem-solving
- Organization
- Strong communication
- Project management
- Data Analysis
- Python, C++, JavaScript